muthootfinance.com 2012-05-24

# Muthoot Finance

**What information do we collect?**    
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number 

**What do we use your information for?**    
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
_To personalize your experience_  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

_To improve our website_  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

_To improve customer service_  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

_To process transactions_  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

_To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature_  
_To send periodic emails_

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**    
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**    
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**    
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**    
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**    
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Contacting Us**    
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
